Inventory of the Benjamin A. Rogge papers, 1945-2005
Hoover Institution Archives
- Clippings, printed matter, notes, 1964-1980 (Folder 36)
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 37-39)
  - American Studies Institute, 1972-1973 (Folder 37: 1)
  - University of Wisconsin, 1972-1973 (Folder 37: 2)
  - Indiana Council for Economic Education, Purdue University, Indiana, 1972 (Folder 37: 3)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1972 (Folder 37: 4)
  - Security Marine Bank of Madison Dinner, 1971-1972 (Folder 37: 5)
  - Earhart Foundation trustees meeting, Washington, D. C., 1971-1972 (Folder 37: 6)
  - Foundation for Freedom seminar, Hinsdale, Illinois, 1971-1972 (Folder 37: 7)
  - Harding College, 1971-1972 (Folder 37: 8)
  - National Association of Mutual Insurance Companies, Denver, Colorado, 1972 (Folder 37: 9)
  - "Business Careers for Wabash Men Luncheon,", 1972 (Folder 37: 10)
  - Ladoga Federal Savings and Loan luncheon, 1972 (Folder 37: 11)
  - Ladoga Federal Savings and Loan luncheon, 1972 (Folder 37: 12)
  - National Association of Metal Name Plate Manufacturers, Oak Brook, Illinois, 1970-1972 (Folder 37: 13)
  - Foundation for Freedom seminar, 1972 (Folder 37: 14)
  - University of Evansville Historical Societies of New Harmony, 1972 (Folder 37: 15)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation and Miami University, West Central Ohio Clergy Economic Education conference, 1971-1972 (Folder 37: 16)
  - Mahoning National Bank, 1972 (Folder 37: 17)
  - Cologne Chamber Orchestra, 1972 (Folder 37: 18)
  - Earhart Foundation and Mont Pèlerin Society, 1972, undated (Folder 37: 19)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the USA Statesmanship conference, 1971-1972 (Folder 37: 20)
  - Economic seminar for young adults, 1972 (Folder 37: 21)
  - National Strategy Information Center, 1972-1973 (Folder 37: 22)
  - Consumer Credit conference, Columbus, Ohio, 1971-1972 (Folder 37: 23)
  - Canton Rotary Club, 1971 (Folder 37: 24)
  - Northern California Economic Seminar, Napa, California, 1972 (Folder 37: 25)
  - San Francisco Bond Club, 1971-1972 (Folder 37: 26)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1972 (Folder 37: 27)
  - Liberty Fund, 1972 (Folder 37: 28)
  - Earhart Foundation board meeting, 1972 (Folder 37: 29)
  - Indiana Bell Telephone Company, Marketing Department sales conference, Indianapolis, 1971-1972 (Folder 37: 30)
  - Central Illinois Public Service Company marketing conference, 1971 (Folder 37: 31)
  - Michigan Bankers Association, Lansing, 1972 (Folder 37: 32)
  - Park-Tudor School commencement, 1972 (Folder 37: 33)
  - Wolverine Club Annual Convention, Mitchell, South Dakota, 1972 (Folder 37: 34)
  - Harding College economic seminar, Searcy, Arkansas, 1972-1973 (Folder 38: 1)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1972 (Folder 38: 2)
  - Methodist Men's Organization (1972), 1971 (Folder 38: 3)
  - Ninth Foundation for Economic Education seminar for undergraduates, 1972 (Folder 38: 4)
  - Southeastern Indiana Chapter of the Bank Administration Institute (BAI), Rushville, Indiana, 1972 (Folder 38: 5)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Illinois, 1972 (Folder 38: 6)
  - Estate Planning Council, 1972 (Folder 38: 7)
  - FALK Corporation, 1972 (Folder 38: 8)
  - Milwaukee Society, 1971-1972 (Folder 38: 9)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Callaway Gardens, 1971-1972 (Folder 38: 10)
  - Missouri Bankers Association, Kansas City, 1970-1972 (Folder 38: 11)
  - Hillsdale College, "Recycling the City: Alternatives to Decay,", 1972-1973 (Folder 38: 12)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, St. Louis, 1972 (Folder 38: 13)
  - William F. Buckley, Wabash College, 1972 (Folder 38: 14)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society, Montreux, Switzerland, 1972 (Folder 38: 15)
  - Seattle, 1972 (Folder 38: 16)
  - First National Bank of Green Bay, 1972 (Folder 38: 17)
  - University of Nebraska, 1971-1972 (Folder 38: 18)
  - Lectures in Mexico City and Puebla, 1971-1972 (Folder 38: 19)
  - Economics Society, University of Evansville, 1971-1972 (Folder 38: 20)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1971-1972 (Folder 38: 21)
  - Socratic seminar on freedom and power, Wabash College, 1962-1963 (Folder 38: 22)
  - Conference on the humane economy, Institute of Paper Chemistry, speeches, 1964 (Folder 39)
- Subject file (Folder 40)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1972-1973 (Folder 40: 1)
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 40-41)
  - Foundation for Economic Education trips, 1977 (Folder 40: 2)
  - Peabody Coal Company, managers conference, St. Louis, 1977 (Folder 40: 3)
  - Air Force Academy, Colorado, 1977 (Folder 40: 4)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, "Role of Business in Society," California, 1977 (Folder 40: 5)
  - Lecture series, Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1977 (Folder 40: 6)
  - Bank Management School for Marketing Managers, University of Wisconsin, 1976-1977 (Folder 40: 7)
  - Athletic Club, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1977 (Folder 40: 8)
  - Texas Power and Light, Dallas, 1977 (Folder 40: 9)
  - Hillsdale College Summer Institute in Political Economy, Michigan, 1977 (Folder 40: 10)
  - New York State Bar Association Public Utilities Committee summer meeting, Cooperstown, 1977 (Folder 40: 11)
  - Keyholders, Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri, 1977 (Folder 40: 12)
  - Crawfordsville Chamber of Commerce Annual Dinner, 1977 (Folder 40: 13)
  - American Statistical Association, economic outlook conference, Chicago, 1977 (Folder 40: 14)
  - Argentina, 1977-1978 (Folder 40: 15)
  - Cleveland Chapter of Ohio society of Certified Public Accountants, 1976-1977 (Folder 40: 16)
  - American Cutlery Manufacturers Association annual meeting, Key Biscayne, Florida, 1977 (Folder 40: 17)
  - Bank Directors symposium, Muncie, Indiana, 1977 (Folder 40: 18)
  - Society of Retired Executives, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1977 (Folder 40: 19)
  - Mindstretcher Series, Carmel, California, 1977 (Folder 40: 20)
  - Will County Bankers Federation meeting, Joliet, Illinois, 1976-1977 (Folder 40: 21)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, McCall, Idaho, 1977 (Folder 40: 22)
  - Employers Association Management Club, 1976-1977 (Folder 40: 23)
  - Southwest Caterpillar Dealer Association meeting, Phoenix, Arizona, 1976-1977 (Folder 40: 24)
  - North American Wholesale Lumber Association, 85th annual meeting, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, 1976-1977 (Folder 40: 25)
  - Philadelphia Society, 1976-1977 (Folder 40: 26)
  - UCLA Department of Economics, conference honoring Armen Alchian, Los Angeles, California, 1976-1977 (Folder 40: 27)
  - Hope College, Holland, Michigan, 1977 (Folder 40: 28)
  - Southeastern Electric Exchange annual meeting, Boca Raton, Florida, 1976-1977 (Folder 40: 29)
    Includes photograph
  - Agricultural Clinic, Purdue University, 1977 (Folder 40: 30)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1977 (Folder 40: 31)
  - Delco-Remy Inventors' Recognition Banquet, Anderson, Indiana, 1977 (Folder 40: 32)
  - Earhart Foundation, board meeting, 1977 (Folder 40: 33)
  - Greater Lafayette Chamber of Commerce, annual dinner meeting, 1977 (Folder 40: 34)
  - Chicago Chapter of Robert Morris Association, 1976-1978 (Folder 41: 1)
  - Harding College, 1976 (Folder 41: 2)
  - Economic outlook luncheon, South Bend, Indiana, 1976 (Folder 41: 3)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Hillsdale College, Michigan, 1976 (Folder 41: 4)
  - East Chicago Chamber of Commerce, annual dinner meeting, 1976 (Folder 41: 5)
  - Peoples Trust Bank Seventh Annual Business and Economics Seminar, 1976 (Folder 41: 6)
  - Sales and Marketing Executives of Indianapolis, 1976 (Folder 41: 7)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, 1976 (Folder 41: 8)
  - Association of General Contractors of Indiana, 1976 (Folder 41: 9)
  - Bicentennial meeting of Great Lakes Caterpillar Dealer Association and Northeast Dealers' Association, Point Clear, Alabama, 1976 (Folder 41: 10)
  - Association of Edison Illuminating Companies annual meeting, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, 1976-1977 (Folder 41: 11)
  - Wake Forest University, Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1976 (Folder 41: 12)
  - Visit from Michael Hurst, 1976 (Folder 41: 13)
  - South Dakota Bankers Association, economic seminar for young adults, Pierre, South Dakota, 1975-1976 (Folder 41: 14)
  - National Hardwood Lumber Association, 1976 (Folder 41: 15)
- Speeches and writings (Folder 41)
  - Speech, undated (Folder 41: 16)
- New York State Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 41-42)
  - New York State Public Utilities executive conference, Niagara Falls, New York, 1976-1977 (Folder 41: 17)
  - Management Training Program, College/University Corporation, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1976 (Folder 41: 18)
  - National Fuel Gas management conference, Clymer, New York, 1976 (Folder 41: 19)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society, Scotland, 1975-1976 (Folder 41: 20)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1976 (Folder 41: 21)
  - Socratic seminar, 1976 (Folder 41: 22)
  - Commercial National Bank of Peoria conference, 1976 (Folder 41: 23)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, board meeting, 1976 (Folder 41: 24)
  - Kansas Livestock Association Convention, 1976-1977 (Folder 41: 25)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1977 (Folder 41: 26)
  - Free enterprise conference, Shreveport, Louisiana, 1976-1977 (Folder 41: 27)
  - Wichita Libertarian Supper Club, 1976 (Folder 41: 28)
  - Kiwanis Club of Dallas, 1977 (Folder 41: 29)
  - LaPorte Bank and Trust Company, 1977 (Folder 41: 30)
  - Indiana Metal Stamping Association, 1977 (Folder 41: 31)
  - The Foundations of the American Economic System, Bellarmine College, Louisville, Kentucky, 1976-1977 (Folder 41: 32)
  - West Texas Utilities Company Management Program, Abilene, Texas, 1975-1977 (Folder 41: 33)
  - Purdue University, 1977 (Folder 41: 34)
  - Discussion Club, St. Louis, Missouri, 1976-1977 (Folder 41: 35)
  - East Central Iowa Chapter, American Institute of Banking, Cedar Rapids, Iowa, 1976-1977 (Folder 41: 36)
  - Illinois Bankers Association, 29th annual consumer credit conference, Champaign, Illinois, 1976-1977 (Folder 41: 37)
  - Second National Bank Customers, Danville, Illinois, 1977 (Folder 41: 38)
  - Liberty Fund, Manne conference, Miami, Florida, 1976-1977 (Folder 41: 39)
  - Ingersoll Foundation seminar on Adam Smith, Rockford College, Illinois, 1976-1977 (Folder 41: 40)
  - University of Wisconsin-Madison, Savings Institution Marketing School, 1976 (Folder 42: 1)
  - Hill Floral Products manager's meeting, Richmond, Indiana, 1976 (Folder 42: 2)
  - Earhart Foundation, trustee meeting, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 3)
  - Foundation for Economic Education summer seminar, Irvington, New York, 1976 (Folder 42: 4)
  - Rotary Club of Cleveland, 1976 (Folder 42: 5)
  - Pulliam Fellowship seminar, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1976 (Folder 42: 6)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Boulder, Colorado, 1976 (Folder 42: 7)
  - Kansas Bankers Association, 1976 (Folder 42: 8)
  - Management development seminar for J. I. Case, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1976 (Folder 42: 9)
  - Institutes for Organization Management, South Bend, Indiana, 1976 (Folder 42: 10)
  - Northern Indiana Public Service Company, Indianapolis, 1976 (Folder 42: 11)
  - Wabash College Alumni seminar, 1976 (Folder 42: 12)
  - History of Economics Society, Chicago, Illinois, 1976 (Folder 42: 13)
  - Executive Development Program, University of Michigan Graduate School of Business, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 14)
  - United States Industrial Council, Sea Island, Georgia, 1976 (Folder 42: 15)
  - Crawfordsville and Montgomery County Chamber of Commerce, 1976 (Folder 42: 16)
  - Rotary Club of Cincinnati, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 17)
  - Steel Plate Fabricators Association, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 18)
  - National Association of Accountants, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1976 (Folder 42: 19)
  - University of Delaware, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 20)
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations, 1976 (Folder 42: 21)
  - Oscar C. Schmidt Memorial Lecture, Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology, Terre Haute, Indiana, 1975 (Folder 42: 22)
  - New Harmony, Indiana, 1976 (Folder 42: 23)
  - Young Presidents' Organization, Pittsburgh Chapter, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 24)
  - Philadelphia Society, Chicago, Illinois, 1976 (Folder 42: 25)
  - Superintendents Workshop, Public Service Indiana, 1976 (Folder 42: 26)
  - Phoenix speaking engagement and Leonard Read seminar in Boise, Idaho, 1974-1976 (Folder 42: 27)
  - Foundation for Economic Education undergraduate seminar, 1976 (Folder 42: 28)
  - Committee for Monetary Research and Education, Inc., 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 29)
  - Centenary College of Louisiana, 1976 (Folder 42: 30)
  - Socratic seminar, Liberty Fund, Indianapolis, 1976 (Folder 42: 31)
  - Young Presidents' Organization, St. Louis, Missouri, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 32)
  - Lafayette Life Insurance Company, 1976 (Folder 42: 33)
  - CEO Community Bankers seminar, Bank Marketing Association Community, Florida, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 34)
  - Iowa Bankers Association annual meeting, 1976 (Folder 42: 35)
  - Ludwig von Mises Lecture Series, Hillsdale College, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 36)
  - Missouri Bankers Association, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 37)
  - Kansas-Nebraska Natural Gas Company directors meeting, 1976-1980 (Folder 42: 38)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society (Folder 43)
    - Regional meeting, Hillsdale College, Michigan (August 24-28, 1975), 1974-1975 (Folder 43: 1)
    - 11th meeting, Kasell, Germany, 1960 (Folder 43: 2)
    - 9th meeting, Princeton, New Jersey, 1958 (Folder 43: 3)
- Writings by others (Folder 43)
  - Economic Roots of Colour Injustice by W. H. Huit, typescript, undated (Folder 43: 4)
- Notes, Industrial Revolution film guide, 1979, undated (Folder 43: 5)
- Lafayette Life Insurance Company, 1975-1980 (Folder 44: 1)
  Includes meeting materials
- Public Telephone Company hearing, testimony, 1972 (Folder 44: 2)
- Alphabetical file (Folder 44-47)
  Includes correspondence, clippings, and printed matter. Single letter folders contain correspondence grouped by name. Includes files related to speeches and writings. See also boxes 1 through 4.
  - M, 1974-1980 (Folder 44: 3)
  - Mannis, Rod, 1968, undated (Folder 44: 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971-1980 (Folder 44: 5)
  - N, 1971-1980 (Folder 44: 6)
  - National Security seminar, 1962-1979 (Folder 44: 7)
  - Northwestern University, 1978 (Folder 44: 8)
  - O, 1968-1980 (Folder 45: 1)
  - P, 1975-1980 (Folder 45: 2)
  - Park School, 1974-1978 (Folder 45: 3)
  - Park-Tudor Education Committee, 1970 (Folder 45: 4)
  - Peterson, William Herbert, 1956-1973 (Folder 45: 5)
  - Ploetz, Eldon, thesis, 1968-1970 (Folder 45: 6)
  - Pollution, faculty committee, 1970 (Folder 45: 7)
  - Q, 1964-1978 (Folder 45: 8)
  - R, 1964-1980 (Folder 45: 9)
  - Ralph Raico at Wabash, 1972 (Folder 45: 10)
  - Clipping on comparative systems, by John Chamberlain and others, 1968-1969 (Folder 45: 11)
  - Rogge (Folder 45)
    - Book reviews by Rogge, circa 1977 (Folder 45: 12)
    - "Book on the Negro," correspondence and clippings, 1968 (Folder 45: 13)
    - Clippings about Rogge, 1977 (Folder 45: 14)
    - Books loaned out, undated (Folder 45: 15)
    - Photographs of Rogge, 1964-1974 (Folder 45: 16)
    - Manuscripts on Adam Smith, 1976, undated (Folder 45: 17)
  - S, 1964-1980 (Folder 45: 18)
  - Stahl, Professor Ingemar, University of Lund, Sweden, 1978 (Folder 45: 19)
  - Stevens, Waldo E., 1977, undated (Folder 45: 20)
  - T, 1965-1980 (Folder 46: 1)
  - V, 1972-1979 (Folder 46: 2)
  - John Van Sickle Club, undated (Folder 46: 3)
  - Visitors, 1966-1969 (Folder 46: 4)
  - U, 1966-1980 (Folder 46: 5)
  - United Telephone Company of Ohio, 1973-1975 (Folder 46: 6)
    Includes correspondence with John M. Lothschuetz
  - United Telephone System, Midwest Group, 1975-1976 (Folder 46: 7)
    See also box 34
  - W, 1972-1980 (Folder 46: 8)
  - World Research Incorporated, undated (Folder 46: 9)
  - Wichita Collegiate School, undated (Folder 46: 10)
  - Williams, Bob, 1979 (Folder 46: 11)
  - Winchester Foundation, 1975-1980 (Folder 46: 12)
  - Y, 1966-1979 (Folder 47: 1)
  - Young President's Organization, Inc., 1972-1975 (Folder 47: 2)
  - Z, 1971-1979 (Folder 47: 3)
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 47:)
  - American Economic Association meeting, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1970-1971 (Folder 47: 4)
  - Crawfordville High School speech, 1971 (Folder 47: 5)
  - Relm and Earhart board meeting, 1971 (Folder 47: 6)
  - Savings and Loan League of Indiana directors' forum, 1971 (Folder 47: 7)
  - Personnel Industrial Relations Association, 1971 (Folder 47: 8)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Detroit, Michigan, 1971 (Folder 47: 9)
  - Indiana State Chamber of Commerce, personnel and labor relations conference, 1971 (Folder 47: 10)
    Includes one compact sound cassette of Rogge speaking on wage price freeze
  - Foundation for Economic Education, board meeting, 1971 (Folder 47: 11)
  - AIB forum, 1971 (Folder 47: 12)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1971 (Folder 47: 13)
  - Erik Ritter von Kuehnelt-Leddihn visit, 1971 (Folder 47: 14)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, 1971 (Folder 47: 15)
  - Indiana Academy of the Social Sciences annual meeting, Notre Dame, Indiana, 1971 (Folder 47: 16)
  - Relm and Earhart board meeting, 1971 (Folder 47: 17)
  - West Central Ohio Clergy economic education conference, London, Ohio, 1970-1971 (Folder 47: 18)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Canton, Ohio, 1971-1972 (Folder 47: 19)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Ojai, California, 1971-1972 (Folder 47: 20)
  - Federation of Republican Women, 1971 (Folder 47: 21)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1971 (Folder 47: 22)
  - C. A. Moorman Memorial Lectures, Culver-Stockton College, 1971-1972 (Folder 47: 23)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Richmond, Virginia, 1971 (Folder 47: 24)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society board conference, 1971 (Folder 47: 25)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1971 (Folder 47: 26)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Marian College, 1970-1971 (Folder 47: 27)
- Photographs of Rogge, undated (Folder 48: 1)
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 48-51)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society regional meeting, Rockford College, 1971 (Folder 48: 2)
  - Conference, Lansing, Michigan, 1971 (Folder 48: 3)
  - Summer Economics School for Law Professors, University of Rochester, 1971 (Folder 48: 4)
  - Speedway High School commencement, 1971 (Folder 48: 5)
  - Reunions for class of 1955 through 1957, 1971 (Folder 48: 6)
  - Class reunions for 1955 through 1975, 1971 (Folder 48: 6)
  - American Safe Deposit Association conference, 1970-1971 (Folder 48: 7)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, board meeting, 1967, 1971 (Folder 48: 8)
  - Public Utility Executive Program conference, University of Michigan, 1970-1971 (Folder 48: 9)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Monterey, California, 1971 (Folder 48: 10)
  - Direction '71, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1971 (Folder 48: 11)
  - National Secretaries Association, 1970-1971 (Folder 48: 12)
  - Ouiatenon Club conference, Crawfordsville, Indiana, 1970 (Folder 48: 13)
  - Philadelphia Society national meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 1971 (Folder 48: 14)
  - University Club, 1970-1971 (Folder 48: 15)
  - Liberty Fund Education seminar, 1971 (Folder 48: 16)
  - Foundation for Economic Education undergraduate seminar, 1971 (Folder 48: 17)
  - Wisconsin Farm Bureau Federation, Madison, Wisconsin, 1971 (Folder 48: 18)
  - Conference with Alex Carroll, Thomson & McKinnon Auchincloss Inc., 1970-1971 (Folder 48: 19)
  - Wisconsin Student Association symposium, University of Wisconsin, 1970-1971 (Folder 48: 20)
  - Indiana Association of Plumbing-Heating-Cooling Contractors, 1970-1971 (Folder 48: 21)
  - Conferences at Brigham Young University, Provo, Utah, 1970-1971 (Folder 48: 22)
  - Colorado Bankers Association conference, Colorado Springs, 1971 (Folder 48: 23)
  - Young People's Citizenship seminar, 1971 (Folder 48: 24)
  - Visit by Paul Adams, 1971 (Folder 49: 1)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, New York City, 1971 (Folder 49: 2)
  - Nebraska Bankers Association, Omaha, 1970-1971 (Folder 49: 3)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation conference, Des Moines, Iowa, 1970-1971 (Folder 49: 4)
  - Cornell Alumni Committee for Balanced Education, 1970-1971 (Folder 49: 5)
  - The Indianapolis Forum, 1970-1971 (Folder 49: 6)
  - National Bank and Trust Company, industrial dinner meeting, Alton, Illinois, 1966-1971 (Folder 49: 7)
  - Indiana Concrete Masonry Association, 1970-1971 (Folder 49: 8)
  - Peoples Loan and Trust Company, Winchester, Indiana, 1970 (Folder 49: 9)
  - National Association of Metal Name Plate Manufacturers, 1970 (Folder 49: 10)
  - Executives' Secretaries conference, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1970 (Folder 49: 11)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, 1969-1970 (Folder 49: 12)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Irvington, New York, 1970 (Folder 49: 13)
  - Park-Tudor Interscholastic Honors Program, 1970 (Folder 49: 14)
  - Indiana National Bank, American Society for Personnel Administration, 1970 (Folder 49: 15)
  - Associated Employers of Indiana, 1970 (Folder 49: 16)
  - Park-Tudor School Honors Seminar Program, Indianapolis, 1970 (Folder 49: 17)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, 1970 (Folder 49: 18)
  - Seminar on Economics of the New Left, Purdue Economic Education Advisory Board, Purdue University, 1969-1970 (Folder 49: 19)
  - Wabash Valley Bank and Trust Company, Peru, Indiana, 1970 (Folder 49: 20)
  - Virginia Clergy Economic Education Foundation, 1970 (Folder 49: 21)
  - Western Ohio Clergy economic education conference, London, Ohio, 1970 (Folder 49: 22)
  - Bankers Installment Credit Association, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1970 (Folder 49: 23)
  - Economic seminar for young adults, Huron, South Dakota, 1970 (Folder 49: 24)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Fall Stag Dinner, 1970 (Folder 49: 25)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society conference, Munich, Germany, 1970 (Folder 49: 26)
  - Bank Administration Institute, Rantoul, Illinois, 1969-1970 (Folder 49: 27)
  - Centro Studi e Ricerche su Problemi Economico-Sociali (CESES), Milan, Italy, 1968-1970 (Folder 49: 28)
    Includes photograph and drafts for speech
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1970-1971 (Folder 49: 29)
  - Institute for Humane Studies, Appleton, Wisconsin, 1970 (Folder 49: 30)
  - Colorado School of Banking conference, Boulder, Colorado, 1970 (Folder 50: 1)
  - Institute for Humane Studies, F. A. Harper seminar, conference on liberty and law, 1970 (Folder 50: 2)
  - Foundation for Economic Education summer seminar, 1970 (Folder 50: 3)
  - Purdue summer seminar for junior college teachers, 1970 (Folder 50: 4)
  - Donnelley Managers, 1970 (Folder 50: 5)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 6-7)
  - Relm and Earhart, 1970 (Folder 50: 8)
  - Conference at Fort Wayne, 1970 (Folder 50: 9)
  - Nebraska Bankers Association Convention, Lincoln, Nebraska, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 10)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation, Norman, Oklahoma, 1970 (Folder 50: 11)
  - Relm-Earhart meeting, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 12)
  - Foundation for Economic Education undergraduate seminar, New York, 1970 (Folder 50: 13)
  - Lawrence, Dykes, Goodenberger and Bower Architects, Canton, Ohio, 1970 (Folder 50: 14)
  - Governmental Research Council of San Mateo, Burlingame, California, 1963, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 15)
  - Mainspring seminar, J. Kipp, Chicago (Folder 50: 16)
  - Middlesex School, Concord, Massachusetts, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 17)